cagreatamerica.com 2014-07-19

# Privacy Policy | Great America, San Francisco CA

**Updated July 11, 2013**

At Cedar Fair Entertainment Company (the “ _ **Company**_ ”), your privacy is very important to us. The purpose of this privacy policy (this “ _ **Policy**_ ”) is to describe the treatment of information provided or collected on the websites where this Policy is posted (each such website hereinafter referred to as a “Site” and all websites to which this Policy applies are collectively referred to as the “ _ **Sites**_ ”).

## Information We Collect

 **-   Creating a Profile and Using the Site**  
We collect and store information that you voluntarily provide to us as well as data related to your Site visit and usage. Some of the features on the Sites permit you to create a user profile by selecting a username and password and answering a security question (collectively, your “ _ **User Profile Information**_ ”). Your User Profile Information and certain other information associated with your User Profile, including, without limitation, your purchase history (see “ _Making Purchases Online” below_ ), will be stored on our servers. You can request that this information be deleted at any time by contacting us at [countmeout@cedarfair.com](mailto:countmeout@cedarfair.com?subject=Count%20Me%20Out). We may require you to provide certain information to verify that it is you making the request.

This Policy does not apply to any personally identifiable information you may disclose publicly in user forums (such as chat rooms, message boards and similar web pages). We are not responsible for the actions of any third parties who collect any information users may disclose in user forums or other public areas of the Sites.

     **-  Making Purchases Online**  
Many of the Sites permit you to make purchases online, such as Day Passes or Season Passes to our parks or Fast Lane Passes. In connection with your purchase, we collect and store certain information. First, in order to identify you, we ask that you provide your name, gender, date of birth, address, email and phone number. We also provide you with an opportunity to opt into receiving our newsletter (described in further detail in the section immediately following this one) or text message updates. When you make a purchase through our online store, we use a third-party credit card processor to process your credit card purchases (see “ _Third-Party Payment Processors_ ” below).

Please note that in connection with the purchase of Season Passes, we require that certain personally identifiable information be provided about each individual who will be receiving a Season Pass. 

_If you are purchasing a Season Pass for a child under the age of 13 you must either be that child’s parent or guardian, or have the permission of that child’s parent or guardian, to supply the required information._

     **-   Signing Up For Our Newsletter**  
Many of our Sites provide you with an opportunity to sign up to receive updates through our newsletter. When you sign up for a newsletter, we will ask for certain personally identifiable information, such as your name, email address, phone number, date of birth, gender and street address. This information is stored by us and used to send you our newsletter. We may also use the information to contact you about other activities, events or products that you we believe you may be interested in. You can opt out of receiving our newsletters at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe” link that is included in every email.

     **-   Booking Accommodations**  
Certain of the Sites allow you to book accommodations at one or our hotels or resorts. To complete your reservation, we require you to provide certain information, including your, name, phone number, email address, street address and Billing Information (your “ _ **Reservation Data**_ ”). If you pay for your accommodations online or use a credit card to pay in person, we use a third-party credit card processor to process the credit card transaction (see “ _Third-Party Payment Processors_ ” below). We store your Reservation Data, along with records of your communications with us and a history of your visits, in encrypted fashion on our servers. In addition, we maintain printed guest folios that include your Reservation Data, stay history and record of correspondence for a period of seven (7) years.

     **-   Contests and Promotions**  
From time to time we sponsor promotions that involve two or more of our parks or locations. Information that you provide in connection with a promotion will be shared among the participating parks. Except as described in promotional materials or contest rules, the information you provide in connection with a promotion will be maintained in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## How We Use Your Information

In addition to the uses described above, we use collected information to make available and to improve our high standard of reliable services. We use such information to:

  * respond to inquiries or service requests and monitor such responses
  * provide information about and market our products or services
  * resolve problems
  * manage the Sites and assess their usage and usage of the services we provide

## Disclosure of Information

We do not sell or rent personally identifiable information to third parties who are not affiliates of the Company. We share information with companies that provide public relations and marketing services for us and, from time to time, with other companies who provide information about available products or services that you may be interested in. We use non-personal information that does not permit direct association with you, or non-identifiable aggregate information about our users for our business purposes and to provide the services available through the Sites. 

We disclose information that we believe is appropriate to cooperate in investigations of fraud or other illegal or inappropriate activity or in response to a subpoena or other legal process. For example, this means that if we conduct a fraud investigation and conclude that one side has engaged in deceptive practices, we can give that person or entity’s contact information to victims who request it. If a subpoena seeks information about you, we’ll make reasonable business efforts to contact you before providing information to the party that requests it, but we cannot guarantee that we will be able to do so. 

We may disclose information to your agent or legal representative (such as the holder of a power of attorney that you grant, or a guardian appointed for you). As with any other business, it is possible that in the future we could merge with or be acquired by another company. If such an acquisition occurs, the successor company would have access to the information maintained by us, including customer account information, but would continue to be bound by this Policy unless and until it is amended.

## Third-Party Payment Processors

When you make a purchase through our online store, we use a third-party credit card processor to process your credit card purchases. To make this possible, your name, address, email, phone number and your credit card’s type, number, expiration date and CVC number and your order total (collectively referred to as your “ _ **Billing Information**_ ”) will be shared via secure (encrypted) means with this third-party payment processor for the sole purpose of completing your order. Please note that your Billing Information is transmitted via secure means to our third-party credit card processor and stored by such third-party credit card processor and not the Company. The third-party credit card processor’s privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the third-party credit card processor’s web site. You hereby acknowledge and agree that the Company is not affiliated in any way with the third-party credit card processor and that we have no responsibility or liability for the services provided by such third-party credit card processor or for the third-party credit card processor’s acts or omissions. Purchasing some items, such as Season Passes, allows you to choose to pay using our “Easy Pay” method. If you choose to pay for your purchases using Easy Pay our third-party credit card processor will be required to store your credit card information for purposes of processing each of the subsequent installment payments. 

Certain Sites allow you to choose to purchase through your Paypal account, rather than through our servers. If you elect to pay using your Paypal account, the link provided will direct you out of our Site and over to Paypal’s website. Any information you provide to Paypal on its website is governed by Paypal’s [user agreement and privacy policy](https://cms.paypal.com/us/cgi-bin/?cmd=_render-content&content_ID=ua/Legal_Hub_popup).

## Choice and Opt-Out

We provide you the opportunity to “opt-out” of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes when we ask for this information. For example, if you do not wish to receive marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference in the Site’s options area. 

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication.

## Use of Cookies

This Site works with a first party cookie that collects anonymous traffic data at the Site. “Cookies” are simple text files stored on your computer for use by a browser. We may use “cookies” to assist in data collection and to track visitor Site usage and trends to help us better serve you. We use persistent cookies to make it easier for you to navigate a Site. If you reject cookies, you will still be able to view the Sites, but your ability to use some areas of the Sites will be limited. Some of our business partners and publishers (e.g., analytical tracking software providers) use cookies and tracking technologies on the Site. We have no access to or control over these cookies or tracking technologies. This Policy covers the use of cookies on the Sites and by us only and does not cover the use of cookies or tracking technologies by any such business partner.

## Account Security

The security of the User Profile you create on any Site relies on your protection of your User Profile Information. You are responsible for maintaining the security of your User Profile Information, including your password and for any and all activities that occur under your account. You may not share your password with anyone. We will never ask you to send your password or other sensitive information to us in an email, though we may ask you to enter this type of information on the Site. 

Any email or other communication purporting to be from one of our Sites requesting your password or asking you to provide sensitive account information via email, should be treated as unauthorized and suspicious and should be reported to us immediately by emailing [spamcontrol@cedarfair.com](mailto:spamcontrol@cedarfair.com?subject=Spam%20Control). If you believe someone else has obtained access to your password, please change it immediately by logging in to your account and selecting “My Profile” to change your password and security settings and report it immediately by emailing [spamcontrol@cedarfair.com](mailto:spamcontrol@cedarfair.com?subject=Spam%20Control).

## Updating Information

You may review, correct, update or change your personally identifiable information on your account profile, including your User Profile Information, at any time. If you are unable to edit your personally identifiable information by logging into your account please contact us for assistance.

## Links and Redirection to Third Party Sites

The Sites contain links to third party web sites and may redirect you to third party web sites (“ _ **Third Party Sites**_ ”). These Third Party Sites include, among others, service providers who have a relationship with the Company and social networking sites that enhance the services and products offered on the Sites. Third Party Sites are neither controlled nor endorsed by the Company. Please be aware that when you enter a Third Party Site, any information you provide, including financial information, is subject to the terms of use and privacy policy of that site.

## Children’s Privacy

We recognize the need to provide particular privacy protections with respect to personal information that may be collected from children on our Sites. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children in connection with the features of our Sites without the consent of a parent or guardian. We request that all visitors under 13 to our Sites not disclose or provide any personally identifiable information. Upon notification that a child under 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information, we will delete the child’s personally identifiable information from our records.

## Effective Date; Policy Changes

Each time you use a Site, the current version of the Policy will apply. When you use any Site, you should check the date of this Policy (which appears at the top of the Policy) and review any changes since the last version. Our business changes frequently and this Policy is subject to change from time to time. Unless stated otherwise, our current Policy applies to all information that we have about you. We will not materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of your privacy without the consent of affected customers.

## Governing Law

This Policy is governed by the laws of the State of Ohio, U.S.A. without giving effect to any principles of conflict of law.

## Notice to California Residents

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by the Company to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. With respect to these entities, this Policy applies only to their activities within the State of California. To make such a request, please send an email to [spamcontrol@cedarfair.com](mailto:spamcontrol@cedarfair.com?subject=Spam%20Control). 

or write us:

Cedar Fair Entertainment Company   
One Cedar Point Drive   
Sandusky, Ohio 44870   
Attn: [Marketing]

## Contact Us

To contact us with your questions or comments regarding this Policy or the information collection and dissemination practices of this Site, please email us at [Marketing@cedarfair.com](mailto:marketing@cedarfair.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Comment%2FQuestion). 

To see the Terms of Use that apply to the Sites, [www.cedarfair.com/termsofuse](http://www.cedarfair.com/termsofuse). 

All trademarks, service marks, and other proprietary materials herein are the property of Cedar Fair, L.P. and their respective owners. All rights reserved.
